I'll be distracted for too long Vivian
chefs I distracted if you want I think
you look so good
I worried oh there you go I was watching
the road you were fine
just wait just wait it gets worse
oh yeah you'd have to touch the wheel
what's up have you guys ever seen me not
at the wheel scope is I'm letting
somebody else drive the car I have
control issues the only reason I'm ok
with this is on posture oh yeah I do I
feel so relaxed with open pilot driving
yeah Oh guys we have driver monitoring
you don't really have to keep your hands
on the wheel you just have to pay
attention at all times and be ready to
take over doesn't take long to move your
hands
it's a secret
why what you're fine my god you're fine
it wasn't it wasn't I was watching viv
you drive way too far to the left
yes stop-and-go works - look we're
driving on super cruise with two zeros
super cruise guys check out my check out
my sin card icon slash Tom Cruise check
it out to get my maverick fans to get my
comedy
great guys
yeah how many disengages have you gotten
that yes a don't do me you can't talk
about the G word yeah this is the secret
good internal oniy we have the good
version that thanks good and doesn't
make mistakes
oh and there's no more six minute timer
because I'm on top being distracted it
has nothing to base so it we could do
that you want to be fifty whenever I
think those where they could Portland
it's good for us to give is commenting
that the light here should have
something to do with anything
it doesn't hit the camera lower - oh no
hands it should have something you doin
anything else complete she be on Twitter
do you want to tell the stuff about your
Twitter yeah light is about battery yo
chase knows on top he also wants you to
hire
[Music]
great great Drive it's some big mistakes
anymore this is a good version of a
pilot this why we need driver monitoring
it's too good
secret cut version all right you board
yet yeah No all right Scopus
read the questions Civic or court no one
Civic right now throwing 69
what happens if you slam on the brakes
completely and lock up tires open pilot
can't do that and if you do that your
dominance where they go with the free on
chase
no is knock off beyond it doesn't
have like a fan or any like good stuff
it's like it it's just it's a phone in
it in a case yeah the free are yeah
that's right pay attention
remember how little attention we paid
during the driver yourself having
awareness to her yeah I know but now we
have to because we have driver monitor
we go back I won't we can't show them
the secret and the scope is I hope you
enjoyed this zero disengagement drive at
all